<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Suryo Wibowo</title>
    <link>https://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Suryo Wibowo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://yourdomain.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ambalat: Brotherhood On The Sea</title>
      <link>https://yourdomain.com/photos/ambalat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yourdomain.com/photos/ambalat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;ambalat-brotherhood-on-the-sea&#34;&gt;Ambalat: Brotherhood On The Sea&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Swinging on its anchored moorings in Bitung Harbor, the Gas Ambalat ship resembles a mother nursing her child—the child being the LPG One ship, drawing LPG cargo from the 107-meter-long vessel. On Tuesday, November 7, 2017, the LPG One took on 600 metric tons of LPG for North Sulawesi. First Officer Andi Rahmat Saleh, responsible for the cargo, frequently checked with the deck crew on the amount transferred.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handtapping Tattoo Revival</title>
      <link>https://yourdomain.com/photos/afp-tattoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yourdomain.com/photos/afp-tattoo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;handtapping-tattoo-revival&#34;&gt;Handtapping Tattoo Revival&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Text by Sam Reeves&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Photos by Suryo Wibowo&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;for: Agence France Presse (AFP)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mentawai tattoos, generally long lines looping over the shoulders and chest and more elaborate patterns on feet and hands, were long part of local culture and signified the tribespeople&amp;rsquo;s close links to nature.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The other well known body art from Indonesia is found among the Dayaks, an array of semi-nomadic tribes who traditionally lived in the jungles and mountains of vast, biodiverse Borneo island shared between Indonesia, Malaysia and Brunei.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under the Spell of Baluran</title>
      <link>https://yourdomain.com/photos/baluran/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yourdomain.com/photos/baluran/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;under-the-spell-of-baluran&#34;&gt;Under the Spell of Baluran&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Spanning an area of ​​250 square kilometers, Baluran National Park, Situbondo district, East Java is one of the oldest national parks in Indonesia and was established in 1937 during the reign of the Dutch East Indies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Baluran is home to thousands of animals and plants. There are at least 26 species of mammals that make Baluran their home, some of which are famous for the wild Javan Banteng (bos javanicus javanicus), leopard (Panthera pardus melas), deer (Cervus timorensis russa), and the shy langur monkey (Trachypithecus auratus). There are also various types of eagles in the sky in Baluran: Bondol eagle (haliastur indus), brontok eagle (Spizaetus cirrhatus), crested eagle (Accipiter trivirgatus). And if we open our eyes wide, we might be lucky enough to find a green peacock (pavus muticus) or a white-bellied kangaroo (anthracoceros albirostris) enjoying their breakfast in the trees.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voices From Kendeng</title>
      <link>https://yourdomain.com/photos/kendeng/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yourdomain.com/photos/kendeng/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;voices-from-kendeng&#34;&gt;Voices From Kendeng&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Joko Prianto could not hide his disappointment with the Governor of Central Java, Ganjar Pranowo. Although the Supreme Court has canceled the Central Java Governor&amp;rsquo;s Decree No. 660.1/17 of 2012 regarding environmental permits for mining and cement factory construction in Rembang, Governor Ganjar has issued a new permit.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;We saw the governor playing with the law,&amp;rdquo; he said inside the &amp;ldquo;Kendeng Guard Action, Semarang Struggle Tent&amp;rdquo; in front of the Central Java Governor&amp;rsquo;s office, Wednesday (21/12/2016).&#xA;This is the third day for Joko and hundreds of residents who oppose the construction of a cement factory to protest. They, who are members of the Kendeng Mountains Concerned Community Network, set up makeshift tents from tarpaulins and stay in them during the day. In the night, they stayed at an institution building or any place willing to accommodate them.&#xA;This is not the first time that JMPPK has held an action against the construction of a cement factory in Rembang. Since the environmental permit was issued in 2012, they have continuously held various protests. Both in Rembang, Semarang, Yogyakarta, to Jakarta.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
